[
  {
    "question": "あ",
    "type": "kana-to-romaji",
    "options": ["e", "a", "u", "i"],
    "answer": "a"
  },
  {
    "question": "i",
    "type": "romaji-to-kana",
    "options": ["え", "あ", "い", "う"],
    "answer": "い"
  },
  {
    "question": "う",
    "type": "kana-to-romaji",
    "options": ["i", "u", "o", "a"],
    "answer": "u"
  },
  {
    "question": "e",
    "type": "romaji-to-kana",
    "options": ["お", "え", "あ", "う"],
    "answer": "え"
  },
  {
    "question": "お",
    "type": "kana-to-romaji",
    "options": ["u", "o", "a", "e"],
    "answer": "o"
  },
  {
    "question": "ka",
    "type": "romaji-to-kana",
    "options": ["こ", "か", "く", "き"],
    "answer": "か"
  },
  {
    "question": "き",
    "type": "kana-to-romaji",
    "options": ["ki", "ku", "ka", "ke"],
    "answer": "ki"
  },
  {
    "question": "ku",
    "type": "romaji-to-kana",
    "options": ["か", "く", "き", "こ"],
    "answer": "く"
  },
  {
    "question": "け",
    "type": "kana-to-romaji",
    "options": ["ki", "ke", "ko", "ka"],
    "answer": "ke"
  },
  {
    "question": "ko",
    "type": "romaji-to-kana",
    "options": ["け", "く", "こ", "か"],
    "answer": "こ"
  },
  {
    "question": "さ",
    "type": "kana-to-romaji",
    "options": ["se", "so", "sa", "shi"],
    "answer": "sa"
  },
  {
    "question": "shi",
    "type": "romaji-to-kana",
    "options": ["す", "し", "さ", "き"],
    "answer": "し"
  },
  {
    "question": "す",
    "type": "kana-to-romaji",
    "options": ["so", "se", "su", "tsu"],
    "answer": "su"
  },
  {
    "question": "se",
    "type": "romaji-to-kana",
    "options": ["さ", "せ", "そ", "し"],
    "answer": "せ"
  },
  {
    "question": "そ",
    "type": "kana-to-romaji",
    "options": ["su", "se", "so", "sa"],
    "answer": "so"
  },
  {
    "question": "ta",
    "type": "romaji-to-kana",
    "options": ["て", "た", "だ", "と"],
    "answer": "た"
  },
  {
    "question": "ち",
    "type": "kana-to-romaji",
    "options": ["shi", "tsu", "chi", "cha"],
    "answer": "chi"
  },
  {
    "question": "tsu",
    "type": "romaji-to-kana",
    "options": ["ち", "つ", "す", "ず"],
    "answer": "つ"
  },
  {
    "question": "て",
    "type": "kana-to-romaji",
    "options": ["ne", "to", "te", "ta"],
    "answer": "te"
  },
  {
    "question": "to",
    "type": "romaji-to-kana",
    "options": ["た", "と", "て", "ど"],
    "answer": "と"
  },
  {
    "question": "な",
    "type": "kana-to-romaji",
    "options": ["nu", "ne", "na", "ni"],
    "answer": "na"
  },
  {
    "question": "ni",
    "type": "romaji-to-kana",
    "options": ["ぬ", "ね", "に", "な"],
    "answer": "に"
  },
  {
    "question": "ぬ",
    "type": "kana-to-romaji",
    "options": ["mu", "nu", "ni", "no"],
    "answer": "nu"
  },
  {
    "question": "ne",
    "type": "romaji-to-kana",
    "options": ["な", "ね", "ぬ", "れ"],
    "answer": "ね"
  },
  {
    "question": "の",
    "type": "kana-to-romaji",
    "options": ["nu", "no", "na", "to"],
    "answer": "no"
  },
  {
    "question": "ha",
    "type": "romaji-to-kana",
    "options": ["わ", "ば", "は", "ほ"],
    "answer": "は"
  },
  {
    "question": "ひ",
    "type": "kana-to-romaji",
    "options": ["fu", "bi", "hi", "ki"],
    "answer": "hi"
  },
  {
    "question": "fu",
    "type": "romaji-to-kana",
    "options": ["ぷ", "ふ", "ぶ", "は"],
    "answer": "ふ"
  },
  {
    "question": "へ",
    "type": "kana-to-romaji",
    "options": ["ha", "he", "e", "ne"],
    "answer": "he"
  },
  {
    "question": "ho",
    "type": "romaji-to-kana",
    "options": ["へ", "ほ", "を", "は"],
    "answer": "ほ"
  },
  {
    "question": "ま",
    "type": "kana-to-romaji",
    "options": ["mu", "ma", "mo", "na"],
    "answer": "ma"
  },
  {
    "question": "mi",
    "type": "romaji-to-kana",
    "options": ["ま", "に", "み", "む"],
    "answer": "み"
  },
  {
    "question": "む",
    "type": "kana-to-romaji",
    "options": ["me", "mu", "nu", "ma"],
    "answer": "mu"
  },
  {
    "question": "me",
    "type": "romaji-to-kana",
    "options": ["む", "め", "ま", "ね"],
    "answer": "め"
  },
  {
    "question": "も",
    "type": "kana-to-romaji",
    "options": ["ma", "mu", "mo", "no"],
    "answer": "mo"
  },
  {
    "question": "ya",
    "type": "romaji-to-kana",
    "options": ["わ", "ゆ", "や", "よ"],
    "answer": "や"
  },
  {
    "question": "ゆ",
    "type": "kana-to-romaji",
    "options": ["ya", "yu", "yo", "ru"],
    "answer": "yu"
  },
  {
    "question": "yo",
    "type": "romaji-to-kana",
    "options": ["ろ", "よ", "ゆ", "や"],
    "answer": "よ"
  },
  {
    "question": "ら",
    "type": "kana-to-romaji",
    "options": ["ri", "ra", "na", "la"],
    "answer": "ra"
  },
  {
    "question": "ri",
    "type": "romaji-to-kana",
    "options": ["れ", "ら", "り", "る"],
    "answer": "り"
  },
  {
    "question": "る",
    "type": "kana-to-romaji",
    "options": ["ro", "ri", "ra", "ru"],
    "answer": "ru"
  },
  {
    "question": "re",
    "type": "romaji-to-kana",
    "options": ["る", "れ", "ら", "り"],
    "answer": "れ"
  },
  {
    "question": "ろ",
    "type": "kana-to-romaji",
    "options": ["ru", "ro", "ra", "re"],
    "answer": "ro"
  },
  {
    "question": "wa",
    "type": "romaji-to-kana",
    "options": ["を", "ら", "わ", "が"],
    "answer": "わ"
  },
  {
    "question": "を",
    "type": "kana-to-romaji",
    "options": ["o", "wo", "wa", "mo"],
    "answer": "wo"
  },
  {
    "question": "n",
    "type": "romaji-to-kana",
    "options": ["ぬ", "ん", "む", "ら"],
    "answer": "ん"
  }
]
